[Script Info]
Title: Exported from a Windows tool

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:02.00,Default,,0,0,0,,Two bytes per character.
